<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<page>
	<content-type>/page/enpagetintuc</content-type>
	<display-template>/templates/web/pages/en/tintuc.ftl</display-template>
	<no-template-required/>
	<merge-strategy>inherit-levels</merge-strategy>
	<objectGroupId>d6337d93</objectGroupId>
	<objectId>d6337d93-e777-4380-bbc1-0b07004b9b54</objectId>
	<internal-name>Mavin supports HCMC to repel Covid-19 pandamic</internal-name>
	<navLabel>Mavin supports HCMC to repel Covid-19 pandamic</navLabel>
	<title_s>Mavin supports HCMC to repel Covid-19 pandamic</title_s>
	<placeInNav>false</placeInNav>
	<orderDefault_f>-1</orderDefault_f>
	<file-name>index.xml</file-name>
	<folder-name>3</folder-name>
	<image_s>/static-assets/images/new/QC FB Ho tro TP HCM 8.2021 A (ngang).jpg</image_s>
	<slide_o item-list="true">	<item datasource="slide" inline="true">	<key>accf517c-92a5-9bc9-b604-f66062be409a</key>
	<value>S</value>
<component id="accf517c-92a5-9bc9-b604-f66062be409a">
	<content-type>/component/slide</content-type>
	<display-template>/templates/web/components/slide.ftl</display-template>
	<no-template-required/>
	<merge-strategy>inherit-levels</merge-strategy>
	<objectGroupId>accf</objectGroupId>
	<objectId>accf517c-92a5-9bc9-b604-f66062be409a</objectId>
	<file-name>accf517c-92a5-9bc9-b604-f66062be409a.xml</file-name>
	<internal-name>S</internal-name>
	<image_s>/static-assets/images/header/bg-app1.jpg</image_s>
	<createdDate>2021-10-01T03:14:44.121Z</createdDate>
	<createdDate_dt>2021-10-01T03:14:44.121Z</createdDate_dt>
	<lastModifiedDate>2021-10-01T03:14:44.121Z</lastModifiedDate>
	<lastModifiedDate_dt>2021-10-01T03:14:44.121Z</lastModifiedDate_dt>
</component>
	</item></slide_o>
	<content_html>&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;Joining hands with Ho Chi Minh city to overcome the epidemic, with the principle of spreading good values and love to the community, Mavin Foundation has donated 5,000 kg of clean processed food to the Program "1 million meals for people in difficulty&amp;rdquo; due to the impact of Covid-19 in Ho Chi Minh City.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;All 5,000 kg of Mavin's products including: sausages, meatballs, spring rolls will be received by the Program in the first week of September 2021 and used to enhance nutrition, serving frontline doctors, field hospitals and charity kitchens. A part of the product will also be used to directly support poor families in the city's lockdown areas of HCM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;The program "1 million meals for people in difficult circumstances", through the Ho Chi Minh City Welfare Center (Vietnam Fatherland Front Committee) and the coordination of units: Ho Chi Minh City Youth Union, Department of Industry and Trade, Business Association of High-Quality Goods... will directly support poor households in more than 4,000 lockdown zones in Ho Chi Minh City, workers lose their jobs, workers lose income due to Covid-19. The program also supports meals for frontline medical workers if needed by hospitals and medical organizations. The program is expected to last from now until mid-September, 2021. Meals are presented in two forms, including necessities and prepared meals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;Accompanying the fight against Covid-19, in addition to maintaining production and ensuring a safe environment, Mavin Group has also participated in many social security and charity activities, joining hands with communities in areas with complicated epidemic situations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;In Hanoi, Mavin sponsored 3,500 kg of clean processed food for the &amp;ldquo;Mini supermarket 0 dong&amp;rdquo; held in the districts of the capital during the time of isolation, joining hands to support tens of thousands of poor and disadvantaged people. In addition, Mavin also cooperated with the Hanoi Youth Union to support poor students in the capital to overcome Covid-19, sponsored 1,000 packages of sausages and 500 packages of fish balls for poor students stuck in hostels, dormitories during the time of social distancing.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</content_html>
	<createdDate>2021-10-01T03:12:24.948Z</createdDate>
	<createdDate_dt>2021-10-01T03:12:24.948Z</createdDate_dt>
	<lastModifiedDate>2021-10-29T09:54:56.239Z</lastModifiedDate>
	<lastModifiedDate_dt>2021-10-29T09:54:56.239Z</lastModifiedDate_dt>
	<date_dt>2021-09-30T04:00:00.000Z</date_dt>
	<date_dt_tz>EST5EDT</date_dt_tz>
</page>