<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<page>
	<content-type>/page/enpagetintuc</content-type>
	<display-template>/templates/web/pages/en/tintuc.ftl</display-template>
	<no-template-required/>
	<merge-strategy>inherit-levels</merge-strategy>
	<objectGroupId>599057a2</objectGroupId>
	<objectId>599057a2-d191-408b-a5ac-a1a165be0732</objectId>
	<internal-name>Mavin’s Chairman talked at Vietnam AgriTech 2021</internal-name>
	<navLabel>Mavin’s Chairman talked at Vietnam AgriTech 2021</navLabel>
	<title_s>Mavin’s Chairman talked at Vietnam AgriTech 2021</title_s>
	<placeInNav>false</placeInNav>
	<orderDefault_f>-1</orderDefault_f>
	<file-name>index.xml</file-name>
	<folder-name>2</folder-name>
	<image_s>/static-assets/images/new/David 1.png</image_s>
	<slide_o item-list="true">	<item datasource="slide" inline="true">	<key>accf517c-92a5-9bc9-b604-f66062be409a</key>
	<value>S</value>
<component id="accf517c-92a5-9bc9-b604-f66062be409a">
	<content-type>/component/slide</content-type>
	<display-template>/templates/web/components/slide.ftl</display-template>
	<no-template-required/>
	<merge-strategy>inherit-levels</merge-strategy>
	<objectGroupId>accf</objectGroupId>
	<objectId>accf517c-92a5-9bc9-b604-f66062be409a</objectId>
	<file-name>accf517c-92a5-9bc9-b604-f66062be409a.xml</file-name>
	<internal-name>S</internal-name>
	<image_s>/static-assets/images/header/bg-app1.jpg</image_s>
	<createdDate>2021-10-01T03:14:44.121Z</createdDate>
	<createdDate_dt>2021-10-01T03:14:44.121Z</createdDate_dt>
	<lastModifiedDate>2021-10-01T03:14:44.121Z</lastModifiedDate>
	<lastModifiedDate_dt>2021-10-01T03:14:44.121Z</lastModifiedDate_dt>
</component>
	</item></slide_o>
	<content_html>&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;Recently, Mavin Group Chairman, Mr. David John Whitehead attended the Vietnam Agriculture Digital Transformation International Forum 2021 as a representative of the Australian Business Association in Vietnam (Auscham).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;The Vietnam Agriculture Digital Transformation International Forum 2021, organized by the Ministry of Foreign Affairs in collaboration with VnExpress and the Vietnam Digital Agriculture Association (VIDA), has the theme of "Keeping up with market trends, ensuring the pivotal role of the economy during and after the COVID-19 pandemic&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;In the picture: Mr. David John Whitehead in a session on &amp;ldquo;Opportunities for Vietnam's agriculture to make a breakthrough&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;Chairman Mavin participated in the discussion session "Shaping Vietnam's Digital Agriculture to 2035", in the discussion on Opportunities for Vietnam's agriculture to make a breakthrough, Mr. David shared among Australian businesses that are operating in Vietnam, there are very few companies operating in the field of Agriculture, including Mavin Group. President Mavin said that the opportunities for businesses to export to Australia are huge and Australians are very open to Vietnamese products. The biggest problem is that Vietnamese enterprises should learn, research the market, regulations on quality, hygiene and packaging before exporting to foreign countries in general and Australia in particular. Currently, the markets Vietnam is exporting to are very difficult markets and Australia is similar. Export requirements are very strict, enterprises must ensure compliance. However, for consumers in Australia or anywhere else, manufacturers in Vietnam need to build a clear brand, ensure stable quality, so that consumers can believe that Vietnamese products are safe and of high quality&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;The Vietnam Agriculture Digital Transformation International Forum 2021 is the venue for public-private policy dialogues between the Government, the private sector and stakeholders to discuss key issues and strategies for Vietnamese agriculture in the regional and world context; thereby suggesting research and proposing breakthrough solutions to promote the digital transformation of Vietnamese agriculture, successfully accessing potential markets. The forum was attended by leaders of the Ministry of Foreign Affairs, Ministry of Agriculture, Ministry of Information and Communication, leaders and representatives of 63 provinces/cities across the country; representatives of ministries and domestic experts.&lt;/p&gt;</content_html>
	<createdDate>2021-10-01T03:12:24.948Z</createdDate>
	<createdDate_dt>2021-10-01T03:12:24.948Z</createdDate_dt>
	<lastModifiedDate>2021-10-29T09:56:12.239Z</lastModifiedDate>
	<lastModifiedDate_dt>2021-10-29T09:56:12.239Z</lastModifiedDate_dt>
	<date_dt>2021-09-30T04:00:00.000Z</date_dt>
	<date_dt_tz>EST5EDT</date_dt_tz>
</page>